<ALL>
<DOC>
<DOCNO> 1 </DOCNO>


 What articles exist which deal with TSS (Time Sharing System), an
operating system for IBM computers?

 
</DOC> 


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 2 </DOCNO>


 I am interested in articles written either by Prieve or Udo Pooch

Prieve, B.
Pooch, U.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 3 </DOCNO>


 Intermediate languages used in construction of multi-targeted compilers; TCOLL

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 4 </DOCNO>


 I'm interested in mechanisms for communicating between disjoint processes,
possibly, but not exclusively, in a distributed environment.  I would
rather see descriptions of complete mechanisms, with or without implementations,
as opposed to theoretical work on the abstract problem.  Remote procedure
calls and message-passing are examples of my interests.


</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 5 </DOCNO>


 I'd like papers on design and implementation of editing interfaces,
window-managers, command interpreters, etc.  The essential issues are
human interface design, with views on improvements to user efficiency,
effectiveness and satisfaction.


 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 6 </DOCNO>


 Interested in articles on robotics, motion planning particularly the
geometric and combinatorial aspects.  We are not interested in the
dynamics of arm motion.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 7 </DOCNO>


 I am interested in distributed algorithms - concurrent programs in
which processes communicate and synchronize by using message passing.
Areas of particular interest include fault-tolerance and techniques
for understanding the correctness of these algorithms.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 8 </DOCNO>


 Addressing schemes for resources in networks; resource addressing in
network operating systems

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 9 </DOCNO>


 Security considerations in local networks, network operating systems,
and distributed systems.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 10 </DOCNO>


 Parallel languages; languages for parallel computation

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 11 </DOCNO>


 SETL, Very High Level Languages


 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 12 </DOCNO>


 portable operating systems

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 13 </DOCNO>


 code optimization for space efficiency

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 14 </DOCNO>


 find all discussions of optimal implementations of sort algorithms for
database management applications

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 15 </DOCNO>


 Find all discussions of horizontal microcode optimization with special
emphasis on optimization of loops and global optimization.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 16 </DOCNO>


 find all descriptions of file handling in operating systems based on
multiple processes and message passing.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 17 </DOCNO>


 Optimization of intermediate and machine code

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 18 </DOCNO>


 Languages and compilers for parallel processors, especially highly
horizontal microcoded machines; code compaction

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 19 </DOCNO>


 Parallel algorithms


 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 20 </DOCNO>


 Graph theoretic algorithms applicable to sparse matrices

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 21 </DOCNO>


 computational complexity, intractability, class-complete reductions,
algorithms and efficiency

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 22 </DOCNO>


 I am interested in hidden-line and hidden-surface algorithms for
cylinders, toroids, spheres, and cones.  This is a rather specialized
topic in computer graphics.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 23 </DOCNO>


 Distributed computing structures and algorithms

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 24 </DOCNO>


 Applied stochastic processes

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 25 </DOCNO>


 Performance evaluation and modelling of computer systems

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 26 </DOCNO>


 Concurrency control mechanisms in operating systems

  
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 27 </DOCNO>


 Memory management aspects of operating systems

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 28 </DOCNO>


 Any information on packet radio networks.  Of particular interest are
algorithms for packet routing, and for dealing with changes in
network topography.  I am not interested in the hardware used in the
network.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 29 </DOCNO>


 Number-theoretic algorithms, especially involving prime number series,
sieves, and Chinese Remainder theorem.

 
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 30 </DOCNO>


 Articles on text formatting systems, including "what you see is what you
get" systems.  Examples: t/nroff, scribe, bravo.

 
</DOC>
 </ALL>